rxwiki.com 2009-04-23

# RxWiki:Privacy Policy - RxWiki

### From RxWiki

Axirim takes personal privacy very seriously. This policy applies to all of the Axirim owned and operated services and websites. It does not apply to companies that Axirim utilizes as third parties or for partner relationships. Each of these companies have their own privacy policies and you are strongly encouraged to look for and review the polices of each and every Internet site that you visit or are directed to. In addition, this site contains links to other Internet sites. Once you enter another Internet site (whether through an advertisement, service or content link), be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites and that these privacy terms do not apply to those sites. Once again, we encourage you to look for and review the privacy policies of each and every Internet site that you visit. 

This Privacy Policy will tell you what information we collect about you, how that information is used and other related subjects about your use of the site. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time at our sole discretion. However, version dates may be posted with a notice banner on the Web site, through our eNewsletters, and/or via email notification. 

The following policies describe how we treat: 

  * Personally identifiable information that can be traced back to an individual person such as your name, date of birth, home address or email address ("Personally Identifiable Information" or "PII") 
  * Information that can not be traced back to an individual person such as the type of web browser you are using or aggregate information such as the total number of users over 65 years old accessing the site per months ("Non-Personal Information" or "NPI") 

## [edit] Personal Information We Collect and How It Is used

The following types of Personally Identifiable Information may be collected and stored by the site and used by Axirim. 

### [edit] Email Address

As part of registering for the RxWiki.com eNewsletter, any other Axirim newsletter (individually and collectively, "Newsletters") or for use on our sites, you will be asked to provide your email address. Your email address will be used to deliver Newsletters and other services and communications with us. 

### [edit] Name, Address

As part of registering for Newsletters or for use on our sites, you may be asked to voluntarily provide your real name, address and other such real contact information. Your name will be used for Newsletter delivery and other marketing communications. 

### [edit] Demographic Information

As part of registering for Newsletters or for use on our sites, we may ask you for specific demographic information so we may strategically target information that is more relevant to you and your interests. For example, we may ask you for gender, race, subject matter interest, age and other information that would aid us in delivering targeted services to you. Axirim may also combine information that we have about you with information we obtain from business partners or other parties. 

### [edit] Polls, Surveys and Quizzes

As part of using various applications on our site such as polls, surveys, quizzes and other interactive features, we collect information including answers and other input. We may share the results of these applications in aggregate with third parties. 

## [edit] Our Commitment to Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important to Axirim. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Web site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our Web site is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

## [edit] Non-Personal Information We Collect and How It Is Used

When you access the site, we may collect Non-Personal Information about your use of our site. We may use Cookies or Web Beacons (both defined and described below) to collect or store Personal Information, or link Non-Personal Information from Cookies or Web Beacons to Personal Information, without your prior permission. 

### [edit] Cookies and Web Beacons

We may collect Non-Personal Information about your use of our site and your use of the sites of selected sponsors and advertisers through the use of Cookies and/or Web Beacons. "Cookies" are small files placed on your computer by the site to hold information such as the times and dates you visit the site, information about purchases or requests and validation information for members-only sections. "Web Beacons" are small, often-transparent, graphic images that may be placed on the site to monitor your behavior while on the site. Every computer accessing this site is assigned a different Cookie. The information collected by Cookies and/or Web Beacons (i) helps us dynamically adapt content on the site or in Newsletters, (ii) allows us to statistically monitor how many people are using our site and the sites of selected sponsors and advertisers, (iii) how many people open our emails and (iv) for what purposes certain actions are being taken. 

We may also use Cookie and/or Web Beacon information to target certain content to you or to determine the popularity of certain content. Cookies are also used to facilitate a user's log-in, as navigation aides and as session timers. 

Most browser software can be set to reject all Cookies with instructions on how to do this found in the "Help" section of the toolbar. This may or may not remove all Web Beacons from a downloaded page. You do not have to accept our Cookies in order to productively use our site. However, if you reject our Cookies, certain functions and conveniences of our site may not work properly. 

### [edit] 3rd Party Advertisers and Cookies

We allow other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within our web pages. Because your web browser must request these advertising banners from the ad network Web site, these companies can send their own cookies to your cookie file, just as if you had requested a web page from the site. Please note that if an advertiser asks us to show an advertisement to a certain audience (for example, men ages 18-34) or audience segment (for example, men ages 13-24 who have viewed sports content) and you respond to that ad, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach. As always remember, we only authorize our third-party ad servers to employ anonymous cookies for ad delivery and anonymous targeting. We will not give any third-party ad servers access to any personally identifying information about you. 

### [edit] Opting Out of Third-Party Ad Cookies

If you want to prevent a third-party ad server from sending and reading cookies on your computer, currently you must visit each ad network's Web site individually and opt out (if they offer this capability). We have relationships with various third party ad servers. Please click here to see a list of third party advertisers and links to their privacy policies and opt out pages (if available). 

#### [edit] Network Address

Each time you access the site, the site may record the network address of your computer ("Network Address"). Although this address is used to identify your computer, it may or may not be a unique address. For example, in some cases, your computer will have a unique Network Address while in other cases the public transmission to/from the Internet may be completed using a shared Network Address that is common to all users on a particular portion of the Internet. This saves the address by allowing routers to use a single public Network Address, and then translates the shared public Network Address into unique private address behind the gateway router. Network Address may be traceable only to your Internet access service provider or all the way to your own location. 

#### [edit] Site Logging 

Every time you visit a page of the site, a small amount of information is recorded on your actual activities such as which page is viewed. This information is used to form an overall statistical picture of the site such as popular content, other Internet sites linked to and the types of web browsers being used to access the site. These logs may also be used to solve technical problems and to investigate abuse of the site, vandalism, harassment or other violation of the Terms of Use. 

## [edit] When We Disclose Your Personal Information

We permit distribution of your Personal Information as follows: 

  * To our employees, contractors and agents who have an express need to know such information in order to provide the site or Newsletters to you. 
  * To third parties designated by you as required to facilitate an online transaction or registration with such third party that you initiate on our site. 
  * In response to a valid subpoena or other compulsory request from law enforcement. 
  * To our officers, legal counsel or their designees when necessary during the investigation of abuse, harassment or other violations of the Terms. 
  * Where the Information is necessary to illustrate or resolve technical issues with the site or Newsletters. 
  * To conduct audits or other similar operations procedures, but only as minimally required to perform such procedures. 
  * Where a user has violated the Terms and Axirim will, at its sole discretion, block the user’s Network Address. 
  * To a correctional institution in which you become an inmate. 
  * Where we reasonably determine it is necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of Axirim, its users or the public. 

In addition, we may transfer your Personal Information to a successor-in-interest in connection with a merger, sale, divestiture or other transfer of assets or fundamental corporate change of the portion of our business of that provides the site or any Newsletter. We may freely distribute Non-Personal Information to any party for any reason, subject to applicable laws. 

## [edit] Opt In and Opt Out

### [edit] Opt In 

You can access most portions of the site without entering any information and without expressly having the consent to any specific question (beyond complying with the Terms). "Opting-In" (and its derivatives) however is the process by which you expressly indicate that you want to participate in the site or one of its features, options, tools or services. In many such cases, you will be asked to voluntarily provide some Personal Information to validate your identity and expressly indicate your intention to Opt-Out. For example, you may have to enter your name and email address, and then check a "Yes" box in order to receive a Newsletter. In these cases, it is common for us to store such Personal Information on the site in order to facilitate your request. 

In the event we propose to use such Personal Information for a purpose other than its original intent, we will ask for your prior consent or we will give you the opportunity to Opt-Out. 

There are certain data fields that are mandatory (e.g., email address and zip code) and other fields that are completely voluntary. 

### [edit] Opt Out 

"Opting-Out" (and its derivatives) is the process by which you expressly indicate that you want to stop participating in the site or one of its features, options, tools or services. In these cases, you will need to provide some Personal Information to validate your identity and take some affirmative action to expressly indicate your intention to Opt-Out. For example, you may have to enter your name and email address, and then check an "Unsubscribe" box in order to stop receiving a Newsletter. In these cases and if your Personal Information is no longer needed by the site, we will delete such Personal Information. 

In some cases, you can also Opt-Out without entering any Personal Information by simply clicking a button such as "Unsubscribe" from our Newsletter. 

### [edit] Default 

For any portions of the site that specifically require you to opt-in, unless you specifically opt-in to such portions, you will be automatically Opted-Out. 

## [edit] How We Protect Your Information

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures designed to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

We limit access to your personal information to those individuals and partners who have a need to know that information in order to support our businesses, products or services. 

## [edit] How To Obtain or Correct Your Information 

You can obtain all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by contacting our Privacy Officer. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows the error. You may also request removal of your information by contacting our Privacy Officer. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

If you have any questions, comments or complaints about this Privacy Policy, please contact us through the site, by email, by phone or by post at: 

Axirim Corporation 

100 Daingerfield Road 

Alexandria, VA 22314 

Attn: Privacy Officer 

## [edit] Emails and Other Communications with Us

When you send the site emails, letters, faxes or other communications, we will retain and store such communications in order to keep a reliable record and validate the information. This also includes any voice recordings we may make of phone conversations we may have with you. 

## Rate this article!

  * Currently2.91/5
  * 1
  * 2
  * 3
  * 4
  * 5

 **2.9** /5 (55 votes cast)
